var questions = [{
    question: "what was the name of the first disney movie ever made?",
    correctAnswer: "1",
    answers: [
        {
            type: "2",
            content: "Mickey Mouse"
        },
        {
            type: "3",
            content: "Lion King"
        },
        {
            type: "4",
            content: "Aladan"
        },
        {
            type: "1",
            content: "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs",
        },
    ]
},
{
    question: "In what year was the first Disney movie releasaed?",
    correctAnswer: "The first Disney movie was release in In 1937.",
    answers: [
        {
            type: "2",
            content: "Mickey Mouse"
        },
        {
            type: "3",
            content: "The first Disney movie was release in In 1937."
        },
        {
            type: "4",
            content: "Aladan"
        },
        {
            type: "1",
            content: "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs",
        },
    ]
},
{
    question: "What type of movie was the first Disney movie?",
    correctAnswer: "It was an animated movie",
    answers: [
        {
            content: "Mickey Mouse"
        },
        {
            content: "The first Disney movie was release in In 1937."
        },
        {
            content: "It was an animated movie."
        },
        {
            content: "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
        },
    ]
},
{
    question: "Who is Mary Poppins?",
    correctAnswer: "4",
    answers: [
        {
            content: ""
        },
        {
            content: ""
        },
        {
            content: ""
        },
        {
            content: ""
        },
    ]

},
{
    question: "What is First Mary Poppin's real name?",
    answer: "Julie Andrews."
},
{
    question: "When was Mary Poppins Release?",
    answer: "Mary Poppins was releasaed in 1964."
},
{
    question: "Who was Mary Poppins based on?",
    answer: "Mary Poppins was based on Pamela Lyndon Travers."
},
{
    question: "What year was the Lion King Released?",
    answer: "July 19, 2019."
},
{
    question: "Name 3 cast members and their roles in the Lion King Movie?",
    answer: "Donald Glover as Simba, James Al Jones as Musafa and Billy Eschiner as Timon."
},
{
    question: "How many Lion King MOvies are there?",
    answer: "There are 3."
},
{
    question: "What or who inspired the story of the Lion King?",
    answer: "The story of the Lion King was inspired by the lives of Joseph and Moses, from the Bible, and William Shakespeare's Hamlet."
}]

